Contact

sindhuureddy975@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sindhuureddy-b64794126 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Management Microsoft Office

Certifications

Oracle Certified Professional, Java SE 6 Programmer

R Programming For Data Science

SAP Certified Development Associate - Process Integration with SAP NetWeaver

Sindhuu Reddy

PGPM Candidate at Great Lakes Institute of Management | Chennai | Cohort 20-21

Hyderabad

Summary

Being an enthusiast in taking up challenging things and with a deep down interest in finance has driven me to pursue MBA(PGPM) in Finance from an eminent B-school.

Worked for Ericsson, A Swedish multinational networking and telecommunications company headquartered in Stockholm for 3 years.

During this tenure, worked as SAP PI consultant and ensured smooth flow of data between B2B and A2A interfaces. Skills in Incident Management, Change Management, Root Cause Analysis.

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services 3 years

Associate System Engineer July 2019 - June 2020 (1 year) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Analyst

Assistant System Engineer July 2017 - June 2019 (2 years) India

Assistant System Engineer Trainee

TechnoLexis Pvt Ltd SUMMER INTERNSHIP April 2016 - June 2016 (3 months) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Developed a website for the company

Education

Great Lakes Institute of Management

Master in business administration · (2020 - 2021)

Goka Raju Ranga Raju Institute of Engineering & Technology Bachelors in Technology, Computer Science and Enginnering · (2013 - 2017)